<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="exhibit2.xsl"?>
<exhibit xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<ID>2</ID>
	<name>Impressive Impressionism</name>
	<startDate>2020-07-01</startDate>
	<endDate>2021-06-31</endDate>
	<piece pieceID="4" imageLink="../../Images/Art/Impression,_soleil_levant.jpg">
		<name>Impression, Soleil levant (Sunrise)</name>
		<type>oil painting</type>
		<creationDate>1872</creationDate>
		<epoch>Impressionism</epoch>
		<creator creatorID="4">
			<name>Claude Monet</name>
			<birthday>1840-11-14</birthday>
			<deathday>1926-12-05</deathday>
		</creator>
		<description>This showcase picture of impressionistic art shows the port of Le Havre, Monet's hometown. It is currently shown in the Musée Marmottan Monet in Paris.
		</description>
	</piece>
	<piece pieceID="5" imageLink="../../Images/Art/Jour_de_pluie_à_Paris.jpg">
		<name>Rue de Paris, temps de pluie (Paris Street; Rainy Day)</name>
		<type>oil painting</type>
		<creationDate>1877</creationDate>
		<epoch>Impressionism</epoch>
		<creator creatorID="5">
			<name>Gustave Caillebotte</name>
			<birthday>1848-08-19</birthday>
			<deathday>1894-02-21</deathday>
		</creator>
		<description>The painting is currently displayed at the Art Institute of Chicago and shows the parisian streets Rue de Turin and Rue de Moscou on a cloudy, rainy day.
		While the scene might seem random at first, Caillebotte planned the painting with multiple sketches. The lantern divides the picture in two halves which each have
		one individual vanishing point. While the painting technique is not typical impressionistic one, the everyday motif and the playful perspective is.</description>
	</piece>
	<piece pieceID="6" imageLink="../../Images/Art/Dance_at_Le_Moulin_de_la_Galette.jpg">
		<name>Bal du moulin de la Galette (Dance at Le moulin de la Galette)</name>
		<type>oil painting</type>
		<creationDate>1876</creationDate>
		<epoch>Impressionism</epoch>
		<creator creatorID="6">
			<name>Pierre-Auguste Renoir</name>
			<birthday>1841-02-25</birthday>
			<deathday>1919-12-03</deathday>
		</creator>
		<description>This painting is one of Impresionism's most celebrated masterpieces that shows a snapshot of real life with a richness of form, a fluidity of brush
		strokes, and a flickering, sun-dappled light. There exists a smaller version of the same picture that is now believed to be in a private collection in Switzerland.
		The big painting is currently housed at the Musée d'Orsay in Paris.</description>
	</piece>
</exhibit>