<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="museum.xsl"?>
<museum xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="museum_schema.xsd">
	<name>The Virtual Art Museum</name>
	<owner>Miraj Brahmbatt</owner>
	<owner>Nathan Bullock</owner>
	<owner>Juan Arroyo</owner>
	<owner>Joshua Murphy</owner>
	<owner>Marius Ebert</owner>
	<address>www.TBD.com</address>
	<exhibit exhibitID="1">
		<name>Renaissance Beauty</name>
		<startDate>2020-07-01</startDate>
		<endDate>2020-12-31</endDate>
		<piece pieceID="1">
			<name>David</name>
			<type>Sculpture</type>
			<creationDate>1504</creationDate>
			<epoch>Renaissance</epoch>
			<creator creatorID="1">
				<name>Michelangelo Buonarroti</name>
				<birthday>1475-03-06</birthday>
				<deathday>1564-02-18</deathday>
			</creator>
			<description>David is a renaissance masterpiece. The sculpture was created in marble between 1501 and 1504 by the Italian artist Michelangelo and is 5,17 meters (17.0ft) tall. 
			The Biblical figure David was a favoured subject in the art of Florence</description>
		</piece>
		<piece pieceID="2">
			<name>La nascita di Venere</name>
			<type>painting</type>
			<creationDate>1486</creationDate>
			<epoch>Renaissance</epoch>
			<creator creatorID="2">
				<name>Sandro Botticelli</name>
				<birthday>1445-03-01</birthday>
				<deathday>1510-05-17</deathday>
			</creator>
			<description>This icon of Italian rennaissance depicts subjects of classical methology. It is known that just like Botticelli's other famous piece ("Primavera"), 
			this painting was comissioned by the Medici family, maybe even the same family member. </description>
		</piece>
		<piece pieceID="3">
			<name>The Last Supper</name>
			<type>wall painting</type>
			<creationDate>1490s</creationDate>
			<epoch>Renaissance</epoch>
			<creator creatorID="3">
				<name>Leonardo da Vinci</name>
				<birthday>1452-04-14</birthday>
				<deathday>1519-05-02</deathday>
			</creator>
			<description>The Last Supper was painted on a wall sealed with a double layer of gesso (a white paint mixture), pitch, and mastic. Nn undercoat of white lead 
			was added to enhance the brightness of the oil and tempera that was applied on top. </description>
		</piece>
	</exhibit>
	<exhibit exhibitID="2">
		<name>Impressive Impressionism</name>
		<startDate>2020-07-01</startDate>
		<endDate>2021-06-31</endDate>
		<piece pieceID="4">
			<name>Impression, Soleil levant (Sunrise)</name>
			<type>oil painting</type>
			<creationDate>1872</creationDate>
			<epoch>Impressionism</epoch>
			<creator creatorID="4">
				<name>Claude Monet</name>
				<birthday>1840-11-14</birthday>
				<deathday>1926-12-05</deathday>
			</creator>
			<description>This showcase picture of impressionistic art shows the port of Le Havre, Monet's hometown. It is currently shown in the Musée Marmottan Monet in Paris.
			</description>
		</piece>
		<piece pieceID="5">
			<name>Rue de Paris, temps de pluie (Paris Street; Rainy Day)</name>
			<type>oil painting</type>
			<creationDate>1877</creationDate>
			<epoch>Impressionism</epoch>
			<creator creatorID="5">
				<name>Gustave Caillebotte</name>
				<birthday>1848-08-19</birthday>
				<deathday>1894-02-21</deathday>
			</creator>
			<description>The painting is currently displayed at Art Institute of Chicago and shows the parisian streets Rue de Turin and Rue de Moscou on a cloudy, rainy day.
			While the scene might seem random at first, Caillebotte planned the painting with multiple sketches. The lantern divides the picture in two halves which each have
			one individual vanishing point. While the painting technique is not typical impressionistic one, the everyday motif and the playful perspective is.</description>
		</piece>
		<piece pieceID="6">
			<name>Bal du moulin de la Galette (Dance at Le moulin de la Galette)</name>
			<type>oil painting</type>
			<creationDate>1876</creationDate>
			<epoch>Impressionism</epoch>
			<creator creatorID="6">
				<name>Pierre-Auguste Renoir</name>
				<birthday>1841-02-25</birthday>
				<deathday>1919-12-03</deathday>
			</creator>
			<description>This painting is one of Impresionism's most celebrated masterpieces that shows a snapshot of real life with a richness of form, a fluidity of brush
			strokes, and a flickering, sun-dappled light. There exists a smaller version of the same picture that is now believed to be in a private collection in Switzerland.
			The big painting is currently housed at the Musée d'Orsay in Paris.</description>
		</piece>
	</exhibit>
</museum>